tvbreak.net 2011-09-02

# Privacy Policy · TV

**Last Modified:** __ October 24, 2009 __

Your privacy is of utmost importance to us here at TVBreak. Rest assured that any information you provide will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

The personal information you submit when registering for the site is treated as confidential information. Such information will not be distributed, traded, sold, or rented to anyone.  
**  
Log Files** :

Like many other Web sites, www.tvbreak.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons** :

www.tvbreak.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.tvbreak.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.tvbreak.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.tvbreak.net’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

**Other sites** :

This Privacy Policy applies to www.tvbreak.net services only. We do not exercise control over external products or services, or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy** :

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes).

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info [at] tvbreak.net

**Tags:**    are there other sites like tvbreak net, sites like tvbreak, tv break net review,
